[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country did Tony escape from at the beginning of the movie Scarface?", "correct_answer": "Cuba", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Puerto Rico", "Dominican Republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Gandolfini won a Golden Globe and a Screen Actors Guild Award for his performance as the head of a mafia family in this famous television drama show.", "correct_answer": "The Sopranos", "incorrect_answers": ["The Black Donnellys", "Crime Story", "General Hospital"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for a unit of DNA usually consisting of regulatory regions and a protein-encoding region?", "correct_answer": "Gene", "incorrect_answers": ["Chromosome", "Codon", "Transcript"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word phobia is of Latin origin.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the expected lifespan of a turtle-dove?", "correct_answer": "20 years", "incorrect_answers": ["28 years", "9 months", "7 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the 10,000 plants native to Madagascar, what percent are found nowhere else in the world?", "correct_answer": "90%", "incorrect_answers": ["49%", "13%", "72%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the man who ran the neighbourhood the boys lived in in the film Sleepers?", "correct_answer": "King Benny", "incorrect_answers": ["King Lenny", "Lucky Lucifer", "Lucky Luciano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Baby plan to do in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Join the Peace Corps", "incorrect_answers": ["Become Miss United States", "Some dirty dancing", "Train to become a doctor like her father"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fruit does not yield the expected scent when extracted and achieving its aroma requires the use of synthetic substitutes.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry", "Cherry", "Apple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Monty Pythons Life of Brian, what group are Brian, Reg and the others a part of?", "correct_answer": "The Peoples Front of Judea", "incorrect_answers": ["The Judean Popular Peoples Front", "The Judean Popular Front", "The Popular Front of Judea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other name of Mola mola, a fish generally considered to be the most massive bony fish in the world?", "correct_answer": "Ocean Sunfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Filefish", "Pufferfish", "Triggerfish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marlon Wayans was in Scary Movie 1, 2 and 3.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]